gamesfree.com 2018-12-15

# Games Free: Privacy Policy

## GF Network

This is an official privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for the free online game website gamesfree.com ("Site," "we," "us," or "our"), an Internet website owned and operated by Games Free Networks, Inc (GF). This Privacy Policy governs only the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") collected by the Site. GF network is committed to protecting your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information collected about you online. 

### 100% Privacy

For your peace of mind: gamesfree.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. gamesfree.com does **not** collect any personal information and our main goal is to provide you with daily free online games. Please keep reading this statement to learn more about cookies that could (or could not) be used by third parties that we allow to advertise on our gaming portal. 

### About cookies

Cookies are local digital text files that can be created by any remote connection that you make in your browser to remote code, script or php files. A cookie can only store text or (binairy) numbers or a combinations of both. Because cookies are just text files, created and controlled by your browser, it's a harmless system for your computer health. However you need to be aware that websites, mobile apps and advertisers are able to write and read certain 'invisible' information on the background while you think you are just browsing some online or mobile App content. Games Free uses no cookies. 

### No Logging

Your IP address is being logged to gather demographic information and to visualize visiting paterns (how many pages you views, gameplays, downloads, etc). Our scripts, html and php codes do no execute to read or write from cookies. We will never log individual details, or anything that might give us a clue who you are. Our webserver has the log configuration disabled and only takes an emergency dump (EMERG log level) in the event of a crash. 

### Sharing Of Information

There are no scripts or programs running on our server that store your information. We allow our third party advertisers to host scripts on our webpages. Third party advertisers might collect, store and use your information. These scripts are not property of our game portal website and are subject to the privacy policy of the third party. Find the links to the third party privacy policies in the sections below to learn more. 

### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising networks to serve advertisements while you visit gamesfree.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Currently Gamesfree is using [cpmstar.com](http://www.cpmstar.com/) and [Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense). 

### Third Party Cookies

Our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. They could create such cookies on any website including this one. Such a cookie could be used to track wheter or not you want to view popups, banners etc on this and other websites that are using their services. Here are the links to our third parties: 

The scripts our third parties execute are not located on our server and their policy might change in the future. 

### Opt Out

You can opt out most advertisers and their cookies [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Please note that the nai service will create additional cookies on your machine as well. 

### Liability

It is gamesfree.com's policy to respond to claims of intellectual property violation within 48 hours. once receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, gamesfree.com will investigate the issue and disable or remove games where is needed. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, then please stop using this site to play games. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

This document is the sole statement of the Site's Privacy Policy and no summary, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid. 

2010  
Gamesfree.com
